choa.org 2005-12-14

# Privacy - Children's Healthcare of Atlanta

## Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is very important to us. To help protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about how your information is collected and used by Children’s Healthcare of Atlanta®. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where we request your personal information. 

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Children’s Healthcare of Atlanta (http://www.choa.org) Web site. On some pages, you can make a donation, order products or register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages are: 

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email address 
  * Phone number 
  * Credit/Debit card information 

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself only to complete the transaction. We never share this information with outside parties. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are never shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and combined information to better design our Web site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our Web site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not use anything that could identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personal information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## Donations ** **

Credit card donations will be made through the **Children’s Healthcare of Atlanta** "foundation.choa.org" site. You will be asked to enter your name, credit card number and billing information. This information allows us to process and fulfill your donation and to provide you with an email receipt. 

As a donor, you can choose to give anonymously (without giving your name) or to provide Children’s with your personal information. 

Be aware that you will not receive a tax deduction with respect to charitable contributions of $250 or more unless you receive recognition of your donation from **Children’s Healthcare of Atlanta.** The mailings will provide for a method to let us know if you do not wish to receive additional mailings. Once you have received acknowledgment, your name automatically will be included in Children’s mailing list. If you wish to receive your recognition, but remain anonymous, please let us know. 

**Children’s Healthcare of Atlanta** works with a third-party credit card company, as do many e-commerce Web sites. This partner manages all customer data in accordance with consumer data protection law on worldwide storage and security (including data handling). **Children’s Healthcare of Atlanta** does **NOT** store usable credit card numbers on its own servers. 

## Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure the information we collect online. Credit card information is not stored on our Web site for additional security. 

## About Cookies

Cookies, or small text files recorded in a user’s hard drive, are employed by thousands of sites to enhance user’s Web viewing experience. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user’s hard drive. Cookies allow Web sites to "remember" users across pages of a Web site and across multiple visits to a Web site. We use cookies for remembering preferences and maintaining information about whether you are currently logged into our systems. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results and a more personalized site experience. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web site’s functionality if you do so. 

## Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Web site from those we know are under age 13, and no part of our Web site is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information 

You can access all personal information that we collect online and maintain by contacting Children’s at [choawebmaster@choa.org](mailto:choawebmaster@choa.org) and requesting this information. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct errors in your personal information online or by sending us a request that shows the error(s). To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies send us an email at [choawebmaster@choa.org](mailto:choawebmaster@choa.org).
